Holiday Road is a tv movie, drama, romance film directed by Martin Wood.
A travel writer, a tech entrepreneur, a devoted mother and more strangers are stranded at
the airport for the holidays, they rent a van for an unexpected road trip.
Dana, played by Sara Canning.
Clay, played by Warren Christie.
Tricia, played by Enid-Raye Adams.
Ben, played by Kiefer O'Reilly.
Ember Craig, played by Brittany-Ellen Willacy.
Dusty Redford, played by Trevor Lerner.
"Holiday Road" is a 1983 single composed and recorded by
American guitarist/singer Lindsey Buckingham.
Written for the 1983 film National Lampoon's Vacation, it was also used in the film's sequels
National Lampoon's European Vacation (1985), Vegas Vacation (1997) and Vacation (2015).
Despite only peaking at number 82 on the Billboard Hot 100 chart during its original
release, it has since become one of Buckingham's best known songs.
Buckingham released a live version of the song on his 2008
album Live at the Bass Performance Hall.
In July 2015, a remastered edition of "Holiday Road" was re-released, both on the Vacation soundtrack album and as a
digital download along with "Dancin' Across the USA" from the original National Lampoon's Vacation soundtrack.
The film explores themes of holiday, based on true story, christmas.
The tone is emotional.